[gunshot]
[Nik] Tyler!
[girl shouting in Bengali]
[indistinct shouting]
[man] He's breathing, he's breathing.
[speaking indistinctly]
Multiple gunshot wounds.
Airway's secured.
[doctor, in Arabic]
We've done everything we can.
It would be wise to consider a threshold.
[Yaz, in French] Sis... it's not fair
to leave him like this.
[Nik] I'm not giving up on him.
[Tyler grunts softly]
[in English] What was that?
- Fuck off.
- [chuckles]
- [Tyler exhales weakly]
- [buzzer sounds]
[machine whirring]
And we're going to hold for five.
- [grunting]
- Four, three, two...
Keep it slow.
[breathing heavily]
Just go home, would ya?
Or what? You'll run over my foot?
That's about all I could do.
Thanks, Nik. For keeping me around.
Really excited about
this next chapter of my life.
[chuckles]
Believe it or not,
it's pretty difficult
to let someone you care about die.
But you fought your way back.
You just have to find out why.
[goats bleating]
[man] Zurab.
[in Georgian]
I just heard from the prison.
They're extending your brother's
prison sentence by ten years.
[men yelling in Georgian]
[lock clicks]
[cows mooing]
[Zurab] Governor.
[chuckles]
Zurab. Always wonderful to see you.
How are you, my friend?
I've been better.
One of our prize bulls is sick.
We have to kill him.
Bury him before he infects the others.
You asked me here to commiserate?
Walk with me, would you?
You said it was urgent.
I just heard that this morning
you signed off on
extending my brother's prison sentence
by ten years.
Your brother threw a DEA agent off a roof.
The Americans are all over us.
When Davit and I were young,
I was to protect my brother at all costs.
My father would never let me forget it.
I contested his extradition to the States.
Kept him in a Georgian prison.
I even allowed his family
to be housed in prison with him.
Let's not forget who put you
in this office. And why.
I'm sorry. There's nothing I can do.
One of our prize bulls is sick.
I told you.
[guns firing]
My man! Looking good. Look at this.
What's with the shirt?
You lose a bet or something?
- Don't you like it?
- No.
I'll get you one.
What's your size, 44 regular?
I mean, you're little bit slimmer, no?
Shut up.
I missed you, too.
He wanted to pull the plug.
Nah, that's not true. She lies.
You would have been doing me a favor.
Next time. You have my word.
[scoffs] It's funny,
your sister said the same thing.
[Tyler grunting]
What the hell's this?
[Nik] A gift.
You're welcome.
You bring my chickens?
[Nik] We ate them.
- What about my dog?
- [Yaz] Oh, we ate her, too.
Jesus, Yaz.
[Yaz] I'm joking. She's in the house.
- What am I supposed to do now?
- Anything you want.
I mean, you could go on hikes,
learn to knit.
You know, try to reach mindfulness.
You're gonna like it here.
All right, brother.
I'll send you that shirt.
What's this?
We packed up your house.
This is all we found.
Your entire life fits in one little box.
Maybe it's time to change that.
When am I going to see you again?
When we have something to celebrate.
Enjoy retirement!
Yeah, piss off.
[engine starts]
[dog barks]
- [whining]
- Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
I wouldn't let 'em eat you, mate.
[commentator speaking indistinctly]
[laughing]
[speaking indistinctly]
[squeals]
[child laughing]
[grunting]
[bell tolling in the distance]
[clucking]
- [woman speaking German]
- [Tyler chuckles]
[in English] Fucking right.
[speaking softly in Georgian]
[Ketevan] Don't wake them.
It's hard for them to fall asleep in here.
Come.
No.
No?
Not tonight.
It's been weeks
since they've seen the sun.
They can't survive like this.
It's hard on them.
Hard?
He needs to grow up hard.
There are other places to hide.
Sure, in here your brother protects us.
But I don't want my son
to become a Nagazi.
The last thing I need is your fat mouth.
What are you going to do?
Drag me into your cell?
You forgetting you're my wife?
Not your property.
Maybe I raise them on my own, huh?
You would not be missed.
[muttering in Georgian]
[crying]
[sniffles]
Mom, you okay?
I thought you were sleeping.
- Are you sure you are okay?
- I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, my love.
Don't worry. It'll be okay.
Maybe Dad is right.
I do need to grow up hard.
So I can become a Nagazi.
This is beautiful, honestly, but the tea?
Not so much.
You're out of milk, by the way.
You lost, mate?
Are you Rake?
I asked you first.
Yeah, but my answer depends on yours.
See, if you are Rake,
then you are the myth of Mumbai.
The legend that got
the journalist out of Congo,
that took down the two gangs
to save the mayor of Rio.
The honor would be all mine.
But I have to say, mate,
you're not living up to the hype.
What happened? You fall off a bridge?
How about you put my cup down,
hop in your car, and fuck off?
That's not very nice, is it?
Not when we've got a mutual friend
who's offered you a job.
I don't have any friends.
Yeah, well, this particular individual
seems to think
you're the only one that can do it.
Me? I'm not so convinced.
Can you even pull the trigger like that?
[gunshot]
Now that's why
you haven't got any friends.
Why don't you go back and tell
whoever sent you that I'm not interested.
Yeah?
What if it was your ex-wife? Mia.
Is that dog wearing a Valentino shirt?
[Tyler] Yeah. A friend gave it to me.
So, Mia in trouble?
No. But her sister is.
What's she caught up in?
Well, she's currently in a Georgian prison
with her two kids.
Her husband's locked her in there.
Can you imagine that?
- His name's, uh, Davit...
- Davit Radiani. I remember him.
Probably the last time you saw him,
he and his brother Zurab were pushing
dime bags on the streets of Georgia.
But eight years later,
they've built quite an empire.
Call themselves the Nagazi.
It means shepherd, apparently.
The brothers were born into war.
Raised in it. Hardened by it.
When they were kids,
they fled the civil war in Georgia,
with only their lives
and escaped to Armenia.
Their uncle, Avtandil, took them in.
To this day, he runs operations for them.
But in Armenia,
they faced a new kind of war.
To survive the streets of Yerevan,
they turned to a life of crime.
Started running drugs in their teens,
graduated to murder for hire.
They believed they were soldiers,
chosen by God.
By the time they returned to Georgia,
they were folk heroes.
They offered their recruits
a very powerful thing... family.
And so the brothers gained
a cult-like loyalty.
And with that,
they basically built themselves
a billion-dollar heroin
and weapons operation.
These brothers have got
all the politicians in their pockets.
They practically run the country.
If it wasn't for the Americans,
Davit would be free.
Location?
They're in the Tkachiri Prison.
Now listen to me, pal,
and listen to me really good.
In my expert opinion,
the problem isn't Davit or the guards,
it's the two warring gangs
that are imprisoned in there,
one of which would just wanna kill her,
but both of which'll wanna kill you.
Now, if I were you,
which I'm obviously not,
I'd want to get in there nice and quiet,
keep my head down,
because the moment Davit finds out
that his family's been taken,
you can rest assured that his brother
is gonna wanna throw everything at you,
and I'm talking
about the whole Nagazi army.
Sounds fun.
[sighs]
Job starts in six weeks. We take our cut,
and for, uh, political considerations,
you're on your own.
If all goes well,
you don't get caught or shot in the face,
I'll meet you on the other side
and give you a kiss.
Failing that? It's been a pleasure.
[Nik, in French] We can get a shipment
of weapons to Seoul by tomorrow night.
And my brother Yaz
will fly there to deliver it personally.
[exclaims softly]
I have tickets to the game tomorrow.
[cell phone buzzing]
Sorry, I have to call you back.
[sighs]
Tyler.
[in English] Yeah, hey, Nik. So listen,
the whole retirement thing
is not gonna work out.
Job came in.
You were clinically dead nine months ago.
Yeah, well, I'm not now. Money should be
in your account pretty soon.
What are you talking about?
Why did they come to you?
Haven't you heard, Nik?
I'm a bit of a legend now.
I think being in a coma
must have messed with your memory.
I tell you what the job is
and when and how you do it.
Yeah, you also told me to find the reason
I fought my way back.
Let's find out.
[in French] You're gonna miss the game.
Fucking hell.
[sighs in exasperation]
[grunting]
[Nik, on radio] One minute to target.
[Yaz] You know,
my hands are super sweaty lately.
I don't like it.
Probably, have low blood sugar.
How do you know that?
- Saw it on TikTok.
- You need to get off medical TikTok.
- [in French] You're already edgy.
- I need to talk.
[in English] Every time I talk,
the phone hears me,
and I get more medical TikToks.
Then you should delete TikTok.
Well, that's a terrible idea.
- [in French] Are you ready?
- Let's go.
[Nik, in English] All teams, eyes on.
Looking good.
[guard 1, in Georgian] Freezing out there.
They don't want to sleep in the cold,
they shouldn't kill people for a living.
[Nik, in English] Phoenix is at Alpha.
Teams two and three standing by.
[in Georgian] 207 unlocked.
You got five minutes.
[guard 1, on radio]
Power is out everywhere.
[guard 2] Going to check it out.
[in English] Hey.
[Ketevan whispers in Georgian]
[in Georgian] Sandro, wake up.
We have to go. Get dressed.
Who is this man?
He's going to take us out of here.
[Ketevan whispering in Georgian]
Put your shoes on.
Where are we going?
I'll tell you later.
[speaking in Georgian]
Dad?
[in English] Shh! Keep him quiet.
[in Georgian] He's getting us out of here.
Your father's waiting outside.
[Tyler, in English] Stay close.
Go.
- Package in hand. On the move.
- [Nik] Copy.
[toy squeaking]
[squeaking stops]
Sorry, kid.
Move.
[whistling loudly]
[prisoners clamoring]
[alarm blaring]
[guard, in Georgian] Code Red.
Security, lock down the exits.
[prisoners clamoring]
Security breach. All guards, Code Red.
Alert, perimeter breached.
Close down the exits.
You'll have to get off your asses.
It's getting busy.
[Yaz] Roger. We're ready.
Fuck! Back, back! Back! In there! Move!
Don't push me.
You're scaring him.
Yeah, well, he's about to be terrified.
[guard, in Georgian] Alert,
perimeter breached. Close down the exits.
[in English] Stand back.
Stay back.
Fuck off.
- [prisoner yells in Georgian]
- [prisoners grunting]
Back off!
[beeping]
[man yells in Georgian]
[beeping rapidly]
Go, go, go, go!
Yaz, I need a way out.
[Yaz] Working on it.
[prisoners clamoring]
Which way, Yaz? I need some help.
[Yaz] Forget Bravo. Too hot. Go left.
To the coal chutes, coal chutes.
Roger. Moving.
- Which way? I'm guessing up?
- [Yaz] Yep. ETA two minutes.
[panting, speaks indistinctly]
- [Ketevan]
- [Nina whimpers]
[in Georgian] Don't be afraid.
Go up, and I'll come up too.
[in English] Let's go.
[Tyler grunting]
Okay.
[both grunting]
[in Georgian] Where are you
taking my children? Motherfucker!
[Ketevan and Davit grunting]
You bitch.
[both grunting]
[straining]
- [sizzling]
- [screaming]
[screaming]
[gurgling]
[Ketevan grunts]
[Ketevan breathing heavily]
[panting]
Tyler. We've gotta go now.
- [guns firing]
- [prisoners yelling]
Take the kids, meet me at Charlie!
- What happened down there?
- Trouble.
Come on, let's go.
- Where's my father?
- [Yaz] Come on.
- [Nik] We gotta go, hold her.
- Where's my father?
All teams move to Charlie. Now! Now!
[bullets ricocheting]
[guard, over radio, in Georgian] Alert,
riot in the square. Lock down the exits.
Alert, riot in the square.
Lock down the exits.
Alert, all units to the prison courtyard.
Close down all the exits.
[guards yelling]
Code Red. Security, lock down the exits.
[prisoners clamoring]
Any route to Charlie that isn't through
the common yard?
[Yaz] Negative, negative.
- Shit.
- Not through it.
There must be another way.
Stay close to me.
Keep swinging that thing.
[guard, in Georgian]
Close all gates. Guards, get to the walls.
[prisoner yelling indistinctly]
[Tyler] Go!
Back off! Move! Back! Back! Back!
[all grunting]
[grunting]
Rake! Help me!
- Rake!
- [yelling]
Rake!
[guards yelling]
Pull the pin!
[explosion]
- [screams]
- Hey!
- [high-pitched ringing]
- [Ketevan screaming]
[all grunting]
[Ketevan] Help me!
No!
Help me!
[guards and prisoners screaming]
[Ketevan screams]
[Ketevan] Tyler!
Help me!
[Ketevan screams]
[grunts]
[gurgles]
[panting]
You all right?
We're at Charlie. Open up.
[Nik] Stand clear.
Breaching in three, two, one...
[Yaz] What took you so long?
- Word's out. We got to move.
- The word's been out for a while.
We intercepted Nagazi radio calls.
They're coming at us heavily armed.
And they know their boss is dead.
- Does the brother know?
- We're about to find out.
[guns firing]
Where are the kids?
In the car. Move. Go.
Hold on.
All right, everyone okay? Kids, you good?
[in Georgian] Where's Father?
You told me he was coming.
[Ketevan] He'll meet us later.
[in English] All right, put those on.
Get on the floor.
[speaking in Georgian]
[Tyler, in English] Shit.
Eyes up. Threat coming from the front.
- [Yaz] Roger.
- [Ketevan] Those are Zurab's men.
[Nik] Team three, move up.
Tyler, we got your six.
Got it. Nik, get rid of these guys.
[Nik] Already on it.
One threat down. One threat down.
Okay, we just pushed the last two
of them down. Drive, drive, drive.
[Tyler] Maintain formation.
- [Nik] Copy.
- [Yaz] Copy.
[Tyler] Contact front,
turn right, turn right.
Son of a bitch.
[Yaz] Shit. We got multiple bikes,
and then an armed UTV, military-grade.
[Tyler] Stack up.
Don't let them between us.
[Ketevan] Nagazi are here.
Soldiers. These men are killers.
Yeah, so am I.
[Yaz] We're hit!
[Nik] Eagle's down.
Keep those bikes off me.
- They must know about Davit.
- Yeah, feels that way.
[in Georgian] What do they know?
[in English] Second bike down.
[screaming]
[Nina speaking Georgian]
- Why are Uncle's men shooting at us?
- Are you okay?
[Tyler] Nik, you got the last two bikes.
Keep them on your tail.
I'm coming in quick.
[Nik] Hurry!
[Tyler] That fast enough?
[Nik] Is that supposed to be funny?
UTV on our left.
[Yaz] Approaching exfil, straight ahead.
Hang on tight!
[in Georgian]
Don't they know we're in this car?
[Tyler] Bravo team, we're two mikes out...
[Nina screams]
- [Yaz] Shit!
- [guns firing]
Fuck!
- [Tyler] Look out, come on. Come on.
- [Nik] Go, move.
[Yaz] Reloading!
Okay, I've got you. [speaks Georgian]
- The girl's hurt! We gotta move.
- [Nik] Okay.
Push right through that door.
On foot. Sixty seconds out.
[Yaz] Take a left!
[Nik] Right! Go right! Follow me.
[gunshots]
[man yelling distantly]
[Yaz] Come on, guys. Keep it tight.
[Nik] Team four! We're on foot.
Twenty seconds out.
[men yelling indistinctly]
- [Nik] Yaz, slow them down.
- [Yaz] All right.
[Nik] Friendly coming through.
Yaz, get us a med kit.
[Yaz] All right. Got it.
[in Georgian] It hurts!
[train clanking]
How bad is it?
[in English] Open fracture.
She needs a doctor.
[man, on radio] Heads up,
got gunships en route.
Heading to the engine.
- Yaz, need you to take over.
- Okay, got it.
[helicopter gun firing]
[Tyler] Got one helo, one's still there.
[Nik, on radio] Copy.
[grunts]
[man 1, in Georgian]
Reaper Team, in position.
Move, move.
Reaper 1 and 2,
you have to stop this train.
[man 2] Copy, moving toward the engine.
Go, go!
[all grunting and yelling]
[screams]
[both grunting and yelling]
[man 2] Reaper 1 is down.
Breaching!
[all grunting]
[gunshots]
Nik, you good?
Nik?
[panting]
You okay?
Better than him.
Shit, get down!
Cover me.
[bell dinging]
We're reaching the end of the line.
Stop the train, Nik.
Brakes are out.
You're kidding me.
Yaz, secure the family. We got no brakes.
- We're almost there.
- [Nik] Hold on.
My team's waiting for us
at the end of the line.
Gonna be a rough landing, hold on tight.
- [in Georgian] What's going on?
- [in English] Figure it out later.
[in Georgian] I'm sorry.
[man] This was deeply resourced.
Lead operative was A-plus.
There's maybe four or five guys
who could've done this to us.
Was this the Chechens?
It's not their style.
They don't organize like this.
Someone wanted revenge.
With your brother, that's no short list.
No.
This wasn't revenge.
This was something else.
[breathing heavily]
It's all right.
- Careful with her arm.
- Got it.
[in Georgian] Where's Father?
There isn't time for this.
Your sister needs help.
I'm not leaving without him.
- Come on. Your sister needs help.
- I'm not going.
Your father isn't coming.
Is he dead?
[in English] Did you kill him?
Huh?
Did you kill him?
[breathing heavily]
[in Georgian] Please, Sandro.
[voice breaking] Oh, Sandro.
[yells]
- Listen to me! Hey, hey!
- Fuck you!
Listen to me!
He was gonna kill your mother. Okay?
It was him or her.
Sandro.
[melancholy music playing]
[boys speaking indistinctly]
[indistinct shouting]
[Zurab, in Georgian] Davit!
- I tried to protect him.
- [Zurab's father] Is this protection?
You fight for your brother
till your last drop of blood.
[blows landing]
[yelling fades]
[chuckling]
[Yaz, in German] Full medical detail.
I need you to meet us
at Donau-City Strasse.
[in English] We touch down
in 45 minutes in Vienna.
Thank you.
We're almost there.
You all right? Need anything?
I'm hungry.
Let me see what we got.
- [speaking Georgian]
- [coughs]
[in English] Don't. She could aspirate.
I know how to take care of my child.
[in Georgian] Calm down.
She's just trying to help.
Don't patronize me.
A doctor will be there when we land.
Try to rest.
[in English]
Since when do you speak Georgian?
Since always.
[Ketevan] She doesn't know?
He was married to my sister.
Thanks for the heads-up.
I was going to tell you when we landed.
Mmm.
[sighs]
[in Georgian] You are a brave girl.
[breathing heavily]
She's mad at you.
It's not unusual.
I should have stayed behind.
My children would be safer with me dead.
Hey, come on. You know that's not true.
We're almost there. You're almost free.
I'm gonna get you some place safe.
I promise.
Thank you, Tyler.
[line ringing]
[cell phone ringing]
[in Georgian] I'm listening.
Uncle... It's me, Sandro.
Sandro? Where are you?
Was my father going to kill my mother?
Sandro...
Answer me!
Don't listen to anything your mother says,
you understand me?
She did this.
She had your father killed. Understand?
She has wanted to take you away
from your father for years.
And now you are with the man
who killed him.
So where are you?
You're a Nagazi. Be your father's son.
Where are you heading?
[in English] Remember when
I first met you in Brussels?
Mia was working for Parliament.
Yeah, you had your boy with you.
I was 19.
He was just a baby. So was I.
Listen, I know what your sister
must think of me.
There's nothing I can do to fix that.
I just want you to know that...
It's the most awful thing
a parent can endure,
watching a child die.
[sighs]
[Ketevan speaking Georgian]
[mouthing in English] Thank you.
[Yaz] Okay, let's hustle.
I need them on a plane in six hours.
Multiple visas.
Merci.
That's nice.
[Nik] You should get some rest.
Papers are in motion.
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm sorry...
I don't need your apology.
I need your trust.
I wouldn't have said no to this.
If it was important to you.
It is.
Thank you, doctor.
I can't imagine what it must have taken
to raise good kids
surrounded by those men.
But you survived.
You kept your kids from harm.
Found a way with nothing. Alone.
I know what it feels like.
I've been there.
Everyone deserves a second chance.
You think what you do is good?
You think you saved me?
That you're some hero?
Doesn't really matter what I think.
People pay me to do things they can't.
Like killing my father.
My mother hired you to kill him.
Didn't she?
No, what your mother did was risk
everything to protect you and your sister.
Save you from that prison
that your father put you in.
He didn't want to.
They'd have killed us on the outside.
- Who?
- The enemies of the Nagazi.
They'd have come for us and killed us.
He brought us there,
so he could watch over us.
- He brought you there to control you.
- No. He just didn't trust my mother.
Wake up, kid.
He knew she would take you and your sister
and give you a life outside of all that,
not stay trapped with him.
A good son
is supposed to stay with his father.
- A good father wouldn't make him.
- At least my father didn't leave us.
[Zurab, in Georgian] It's the most
important thing I'll ever ask you to do.
To rectify this desecration.
This filth came to our home
and murdered our family.
Our brothers.
By God's law, he must die by our hand.
You are my brothers. My life is yours.
I'll follow you to the end.
My life is yours.
And mine.
[speaks Georgian]
You're throwing their lives away.
This path doesn't end well.
"You fight for your brother
till your last drop of blood."
I haven't forgotten my father's lesson.
Have you?
[in English] You and my son
met once before.
Played on the beach together.
I don't know if you remember.
He'd nearly be as old as you are now.
Last time I saw him,
he was sitting in a hospital bed
and drawing.
He had papers and crayons
spread out everywhere.
He used to love to draw.
I came to say goodbye
'cause I was shipping out to Afghanistan,
and I knew I might not see him again,
he might not be alive when I got back.
So I came to the hospital,
and there he was on the bed, drawing.
And you're right, I...
And I left.
Last thing my kid remembers
is me walking out on him.
But your mom, she stayed.
She stayed with your father for years
to keep you safe.
Even after all the things he did to her,
what you did and didn't see.
She stayed to keep you
and your sister safe.
I'm not gonna lie to you, mate,
shit's gonna get harder,
but you'll have to take care of her.
She's gonna need you.
So you can be there for her
like she was for you.
Or let your father's lies consume you.
It's on you, mate.
[voice breaking]
He wasn't always like this.
I'm sorry.
- Nah, it's okay.
- No.
He's coming.
[helicopter approaching in the distance]
Oh, kid, what did you do?
Attack team from north side. Move!
Pack it up. Let's go.
- We gotta move.
- What's going on?
They found us.
Take the elevator down.
Walk calmly out the front door.
I'll get to the garage,
use the armored cars to punch through.
- Let's go.
- [gun cocks]
[in Georgian] Up or down?
They'll come down. More options.
The children?
MEET ME IN THE BACK ALLEY.
- What did you do?
- I'm sorry, Mama...
Sandro... What did you do? How could you?!
He doesn't care about you!
He's gonna kill us!
The Nagazi are my family.
[breathing heavily]
[voice breaking] I am your family.
Nina is your family!
[helicopter whirring]
- [in English] Get down!
- [Nik] Get down!
Come on.
[Tyler] Chopper on the roof.
They're pinching us in.
Let's go! Come on. Move. Move.
[Ketevan speaks Georgian]
- We'll punch a hole. Break you through.
- Thank you.
[Tyler] Go. Get in the car.
[speaking Georgian]
[engine starts]
Sandro!
- Sandro! Kid, wait!
- I got him.
Yaz! No!
Shit.
- He's going to his uncle.
- Nik, stay in radio contact.
[siren wailing]
[woman screaming]
[people screaming]
[officers exclaim]
- [people screaming]
- [tires screech]
[in German] We need backup!
- Keep going, Nik. Get the boy.
- Tyler...
Heads down.
[Nina screams]
Hey! Come here!
Hey!
Come back here.
Sandro.
[Yaz] Come on, kid. Come back.
Hey, kid, trust me.
You don't want to do that.
[in Georgian] Come, boy.
[in English] Come back to your mother.
[in Georgian] Don't listen to him.
[Yaz] Your mother did all this
to protect you. Come back.
[in Georgian] Come back to us.
Sandro.
Come to your family.
[Zurab yells in Georgian]
Shit!
[Yaz] Nik!
[both grunting]
- [gunshots]
- Nik, are you all right?
Putain.
[groans]
[in Georgian] It wasn't my mother's fault.
She just wanted us to get out of there.
Get in the car. Stay here.
Watch the boy.
[in English] Go!
Frag out.
[Zurab shouts in Georgian]
- [gunshots]
- [grunts]
[groans]
[car alarms blaring]
[yells]
[both grunting]
[bomb beeping]
- You all right?
- [breathing heavily]
Tyler, he's got the kid.
Nik and I are on foot.
Heading streetside. We need evac.
[Tyler] Hold on.
[sirens wailing]
[in Georgian]
Team three, take them out. Quick.
[officers yelling]
They're up top.
Force them back into the building.
[in English] Tyler, we're pinned down!
Hurry up!
[Tyler, on radio] Coming to you.
[grunts]
[Zurab, in Georgian] Pin him in!
[Nina screams]
[in English] Stay here.
[in German] Do we have
permission to engage?
Shooters on the roof.
[officer, on radio] Cleared to engage.
[man, in Georgian] Police!
[Zurab shouts in Georgian]
[grunts]
[speaks in Georgian]
[both grunt]
- Nik! Get to the roof. Take their wings.
- Copy.
[Zurab shouts in Georgian]
- [in English] Ready? Move!
- [Nik] Go!
[shouts in Georgian]
Reload!
[in English] Stay with me.
[shouts in Georgian]
[both panting]
[in English] Tyler, we're at the elevator.
Coming to the roof.
Move!
[Ketevan speaking Georgian]
[in English] We're heading up now.
We're right behind you.
[Yaz] Copy.
[Tyler] They're squeezing us in.
Secure the chopper.
I'll sweep up from the floor below.
Split their focus.
We'll clear out,
and all get matching shirts. Cool?
And wear them this time.
[scoffs] Not a chance.
- Team one, they're headed to you.
- We're ready.
Sergo, Konstantine, secure the entrance.
Everyone else, up top.
Hey.
[in Georgian] You okay?
- [speaks Georgian]
- You're gonna be okay.
[Ketevan] I am sorry.
I'm so sorry I dragged you into this.
- [in English] Hey.
- [crying]
There's nothing to be sorry about.
We'll get you out of here, okay?
Gonna get you back to your sister.
[in Georgian]
Is he going to kill my mother?
If you wanted her alive,
you shouldn't have called.
[dinging]
[grunts]
Yaz! Need you on the 57th floor.
South side.
Stay here.
Go get the family. I got this.
Go!
[yells]
[grunting]
[treadmill beeps]
[Tyler straining]
I'm going to enjoy killing you.
Yeah, get in line.
[yells]
You must really care for this woman.
Good.
Now you know how it feels
to lose someone you love.
[both grunting]
[clicks]
Do you trust me?
Should I not?
[both grunting]
Get the family.
[in Georgian] Traitor!
- [groans]
- Yaz!
Yeah. Are you good?
Mmm-hmm.
Let's go. Let's go.
Go, go.
[both grunting]
[glass cracking]
Got the family. Heading up.
On my way.
[Yaz] Let's go. Let's go.
- [gunshots]
- [groans]
[grunts]
[Tyler] Yaz?
Shit.
[Nik] Yaz.
Get us up, Nik! Get us up!
[whimpering]
Tyler, what's going on?
Keep us flying, Nik. Just keep us flying.
- [Tyler] I got you.
- I can't breathe.
- Sorry. Okay...
- Yaz!
Look, buddy, hey. Yaz! Yaz!
Yaz, look at me, buddy. Eyes on me.
Okay, you stay with me, buddy. I got you!
[imperceptible]
Yeah, man...
[Nik] Yaz!
[imperceptible]
[Nik sobbing] No!
[in Georgian] What happened?
[Zurab's father's voice echoing]
- [news anchors speaking German on TV]
- [Tyler groans]
[sobbing]
- Mia!
- Keto.
- Mia.
[in Georgian]
I thought I'd never see you again.
[both speaking indistinctly]
[Avtandil]
The whole country is looking for us.
Then go, get on the plane.
We lost ten Nagazi today.
Good soldiers.
It's enough.
Don't be afraid.
It'll be fine.
Be an example to Sandro.
You're no good to him dead,
or rotting in an Austrian prison.
How can I be an example to Sandro,
if I run away?
Let's ask God.
"Fear not, for I'm with you."
"The Lord is near to the brokenhearted."
I know, I've read it.
I once believed God took your hearing,
so he could whisper right into your ear.
But now you only hear your rage.
You know who my father
used to compare you to?
Do you remember the cricket
from the movie?
The one who sits on the boy's nose.
Always chirping nonsense in his ear.
Chirping and chirping, again and again.
Do you remember it?
And where is your father now?
Where is your brother?
[gunshot]
I always knew
there was a bullet waiting for me,
but not from your gun.
Sweetheart.
You got so big.
[speaks Georgian]
Aunt Mia's going to take us
somewhere safe. Okay?
Is Sandro coming?
[door opens]
[in English] Made you a coffee
if you want. Milk, two sugars.
Look, if I had anyone else to ask,
I would have.
Yeah, I know. It's, um... It's good.
Look, I know you don't want to hear this...
I'm sorry I wasn't there.
I'm sorry I didn't stay. I should have...
Should have been there for you, for him.
You're right. I don't wanna hear it.
[sighs]
Why didn't you stay?
Well, they needed me in, um...
in Kandahar and...
We needed you.
- Because I was deployed...
- Why didn't you stay?
- Well, I had orders, and... so I couldn't...
- Bullshit.
- No, why didn't you stay?
- I couldn't...
I couldn't fix it.
I couldn't fucking fix it.
[sighs]
[cell phone buzzing]
[Zurab] I'm standing here,
staring at my plane.
- But I can't get on it.
- Yeah, why is that?
Because I could never live my life
knowing you're still around.
Where's the boy?
You think the boy
wants anything to do with you?
I think he's confused.
Why don't you tell me where you are,
and we can finish what we started?
Want to negotiate?
At the airfield. By St. George's Church.
I'm not coming to negotiate.
[tense music playing]
[engine starts]
[knocking at car door]
Don't do this.
Stay with her. Get them out.
Open the door. Open the door!
Tyler!
[beeping]
Sergo! Sergo!
[speaking Georgian]
Hurry up.
[groaning]
[panting]
[grunting]
[Zurab, in English] Come.
You want the boy. Here he is.
[Tyler] This is between me and you.
Let him go.
[Zurab] No, he stays here.
You know, God gave me a mission
to rain vengeance upon your head.
Sometimes there is a great sacrifice
in enacting God's will.
[beeping]
He's just a kid.
Doubt me.
Pull the trigger,
consume yourself in a lifetime of guilt.
Life is slowly draining from your body.
I've had worse.
[in Georgian] Go. Take his gun.
Don't make me tell you again.
[in English] Give him the weapon.
Now weigh the gun in your hand,
and point at his head.
You're a coward.
[snickers]
Coward?
Cowardice is killing an unarmed man
in the bowels of a prison.
[in Georgian]
I said to point the gun at him.
This is the man who killed your father.
Avenge him.
[speaks Georgian]
Pull the trigger.
[in English] It's okay, mate.
[breath trembling]
[in Georgian] Disappointing.
[door squeaks softly]
[in English] Put the gun down.
Put the gun down.
Oh, you can exact retribution
for your brother,
but it will be at the cost
of his life right now.
So put the gun down!
[in French]
I'm going to blow his asshole face off.
[Tyler, in English] Nik,
the boy.
[breathes heavily]
Good girl.
Fuck you.
[both grunt]
[groans]
[both grunting]
- [straining]
- [grunts]
[screams]
[yelling]
[Tyler groans]
[bomb beeping]
[both grunting]
- [yells]
- [Tyler screams]
[Nik groans]
[beeping continues]
[Tyler grunting]
[grunts]
I'm... I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
[grunts]
[grunts, groans]
[panting]
[screaming]
[both panting]
I will not...
stop.
- Hey.
How are they?
Good. Safe.
They're in witness protection.
I helped her broker a deal
with the Americans.
She gave them trade routes,
bank accounts, names.
The Americans froze their assets though.
Took it all.
If you go to my cabin in the third
floorboard back from the fireplace,
there's a million in cash.
You can give it to them.
I... I came here because I wanted...
Thank you, Mia.
I know, I never said that.
I never said "thank you"
for doing what I... couldn't.
His last image of you
wasn't you walking out on him.
It was you going off to save people.
And he was so brave, Tyler, when it ended.
He said, "I want to be brave like Dad."
That's how he saw you.
Goodbye, Tyler.
[man] It's like the goddamn
Sound of Music out here. Isn't it?
Told you not to get caught.
Shit happens, eh?
What if I could get you out?
How does that work?
Come and do another job for us.
Not without my team.
I'm not leaving her behind.
[chuckles]
Yeah. Thought you might say that.
[car approaching]
[man] Rake.
Rake. That's such a fun name to say.
You never told me your name.
Is it as much fun?
My name doesn't matter.
Yeah? What does?
Who I work for.
Who's that?
A gnarly motherfucker.
You'll love him.